PERFECT CROWN
THIS IS A WORK OF FICTION
CHILD ACTORS AND ANIMALS WERE FILMED SAFELY
Your Royal Highness, is your scandal with CEO Seong Huiju true?
Why was a doctor called to the hotel?
Would you care to respond?
Are you officially confirming it?
Are the rumors true?
- Is it true? - Do you acknowledge it?
Oh. It's Seong Huiju!
Prepare yourself to become the Grand Prince's wife.
You will be up against…
…the whole nation.
Before all that,
shall we see what you can do?
Well then,
how about a generous donation to the Crown?
Sway public opinion first.
The palace will remain silent.
Hmm.
You had me worried for a second.
Move faster already.
GRAND PRINCE I-AN ENTERS PALACE WITH CEO SEONG HUIJU
Today, I'm going to show you the trending "Seong Huiju makeup" tutorial,
the look that stole Prince I-AN's heart.
"COMMONER" SEONG HUIJU ENTERS PALACE WHAT'S NEXT?
PERFECT CROWN
EPISODE 3 :cue
Welcome, Your Royal Highness.
Her Majesty is looking for you.
- I will pay her a visit tomorrow. - Your Royal Highness.
Her Majesty has even postponed her meal and is waiting.
The matter seems rather urgent.
Perhaps you can see her now.
Wait for me. I shall be back.
By myself?
Are you afraid?
No.
Take a nap if you are tired.
Okay.
He's even a good actor.
NOT PRIVY TO CEO'S PRIVATE LIFE, A CAUSE FOR CELEBRATION IF TRUE
Your Majesty.
Grand Prince I-AN has arrived.
Is such a delay necessary?
- I did not know you were looking for me. - Not that.
I ask whether such a delay is necessary
before you offer an apology for causing such a scandal.
I see.
I hear you brought that maiden with you.
I understand the need to align stories,
but did you have to bring her all the way to the palace?
Have you any intention
of denying it?
It appears I do not.
I plan to confirm
both the tryst at the hotel and the possibility of marriage.
Are you throwing a tantrum?
Premarital pregnancy…
You can rest assured
that no such tantrum will be thrown.
Your Royal Highness, Public Affairs has reached out.
What are you doing here?
- Pardon? - You should be guarding Anhwadang Hall.
To keep an eye on Seong Huiju.
But…
My apologies.
Seong Huiju.
Oh. You're here.
Uncle.
See, I told you it'd be spicy.
Have some water.
I am fine.
Your Majesty, what are you doing here at this late hour? :cue
He said he was having trouble sleeping--
I did not ask you.
I was having trouble sleeping.
So I came by.
What does having trouble sleeping
have to do with this?
She said a full belly would help me fall asleep.
Come in, Court Lady Jung.
Your Majesty.
Shall I escort you to Queen Mother's quarters?
You couldn't just let him finish it in peace?
I mean, come on.
A bowl of ramyeon wouldn't have taken that long to finish.
And if he suffers indigestion?
You would be wholly to blame.
And if Queen Mother is angered?
All that over a measly bowl of ramyeon?
The Queen Mother…
denied the request.
Well…
we expected as much.
But you know, it still doesn't feel great.
Like I'm being bullied by my in-laws.
Wait! Hold on a second.
What will you do if my in-laws really bully me?
I mean, just look at how things are unfolding already.
Let's say the Queen Mother and I got into a fight.
Would you take my side?
Why aren't you answering?
Will you take their side and not mine
because they're your family?
I will take your side.
I must appear
insanely infatuated with you…
…for people to believe
this absurd marriage is genuine.
No, Your Royal Highness.
You cannot let her sleep in Anhwadang Hall.
We have no choice with the palace gates shut.
We have the quarters of the palace attendants.
But she is not a palace attendant.
I shall look for other vacant quarters--
No need.
Get her a change of clothes as well.
Clothes?
Huh?
Can I get something that's 100% cotton?
My skin's a little sensitive.
:cue
Will you not even consider the sofa?
No. This is perfectly fine.
The sofa would be perfectly fine too.
Then you should go. That'd be perfect.
Stop!
My goodness.
- Oh, my. -  Your Royal Highness.
Your Royal Highness!
Stay still!
Your Royal Highness.
-  Your Royal Highness! - What? Stay still…
My goodness.
Do you know what time it is right now?
It's unlike you to sleep in like this.
Ms. Seong is already on her way to work.
With a pep in her step, at that.
You didn't change?
No. Something wrong?
Are you trying to show off that you spent the night out?
Did you not have time to change?
I did have the time, but had no desire to.
I wanted people to know
I didn't go home last night.
Oh.
Are you quite pleased?
Yes, I much prefer this over yakgwa.
Did you sleep well last night?
Did you dream about the late king again?
Hmm.
I am afraid.
Do not worry, Your Highness the Crown Prince.
- You will have me by your side-- -  You cannot, Your Royal Highness.
Your Royal Highness.
- The wedding rites are about to commence. - So?
You should take your place out there.
Should His Majesty learn of this…
you will be punished for dishonoring the Crown Prince.
Are you prepared for that?
Your Royal Highness!
I clearly gave you a chance.
Whatever happens from here on… :cue
you will have to…
deal with it yourself.
I am scared.
Ah. Do not worry, Your Majesty.
You will always have your grandfather by your side.
Go on.
FAMILY APPRECIATION MONTH EVENT REPORT
A ROYAL SCANDAL? SEONG HUIJU HIT THE JACKPOT…
"A royal child out of wedlock? That's insane."
That's right. It's totally insane.
"Prince I-AN and Seong Huiju make a terrible couple."
No, we totally make the hottest couple.
Can you stop reading the comments?
Why? I need to monitor the situation closely.
"Guys, maybe she has something on him?
Why else would he date a commoner?"
Why do you think, loser?
Because I'm worth dating. That's why.
- You little… - Here.
The top five trending keywords are all about you.
Your hotel outfit is already sold out.
Really?
Call the PR team.
The PR team? Why?
Why else?
It's time to take back the number-one spot in sales.
How can you even think about that right now?
It's marriage, not retirement.
Oh. Jeongwoo?
Hello, sir.
-  Isn't he so handsome? - Super handsome!
This is my first time seeing Prime Minister Min in person.
He looks like a total celebrity.
Right. But what's he doing here?
Maybe because of the scandal?
- Oh! That must be-- - Why is no one working?
You're really going to marry him?
- Yeah. - His Royal Highness?
Yeah.
I thought you two had just met.
Can't you just stick to dating?
But I want to be with him all the time.
-  Huiju… - I want to wake up next to him
every day.
I hear the royal family
wants to marry him off to someone else.
That's why I have to marry him right now.
While you're the Prime Minister.
I need you to get
my marriage approved.
We're planning to invite the top 300 patrons in the country.
-  What are the criteria? - Your Royal Highness.
The Queen Mother has taken to her sickbed.
All of a sudden?
Perhaps it's a ploy to prevent an official statement.
The palace cannot speak of celebrations while a royal elder lies ill.
JUNIOR ALUM
Understood. You may leave.
Your Royal Highness!
I hear you fine. Lower your voice.
Did you read the article?
Right before it was pulled.
It was taken down at lightning speed.
The Queen Mother has been very busy.
I guess even nobles can move quickly
when they want to.
:cue
Seong Huiju?
Oh?
You sly fox!
You dare try to seduce His Royal Highness!
- "Fox"? - Yeah, you fox!
- Oh, my gosh! - Stay away from His Royal Highness!
- Get lost! - Hey, good job.
Seong Huiju?
Should we? Should we not?
Come here, you brats.
- We could throw them all. - "Come here, you brats!"
Get over here now!
Your Royal Highness.
What is all that?
Is it not obvious? These are your duties.
- All of it? - All of it.
- That cannot be true. - It most certainly is.
These are the duties you are to carry out on His Majesty's behalf.
These are the Queen Mother's… Goodness. This stack is quite heavy.
These are the Queen Mother's duties you are to carry out
in her absence.
And these are your duties that accumulated while you were away.
- You got this. - Get out.
Yes, sir.
Let's go. Off we go.
You little brats should be in school with your noses in books.
Eyes down!
Does Prince I-AN put food on your table?
He may not feed us, but he gives us money.
- Right. - We're royal scholarship students.
That money was for your studies.
Do you think he wanted you to spend that money buying eggs to throw?
And you, Hyerin.
Why did you assume I seduced him?
Isn't it obvious?
Why, you little…
So young and already full of prejudice.
If I had it my way,
I'd give you hell and take legal action for pulling something like this…
Come here.
But right now,
your big sis here has a major undertaking ahead of her.
So I'll let it slide just this once.
Got it?
- Answer me! - Yes, ma'am!
Off you go.
Almighty God.
Please have mercy on us,
forgive us our sins,
and bring us to everlasting life.
Amen.
You said you couldn't come for a while.
I heard my friend is getting married, so I came to pray.
That friend is very lucky to have you praying for her happiness.
I'm not so sure.
I prayed for something sinful.
Something sinful?
I do not feel inclined
to congratulate her.
But I don't want to stop her either.
Even if I don't think it's right…
Damn it.
Where did that punk hide it?
If that's what she wants…
- Ma'am. -  Hey, Jeongwoo.
Are you running an errand?
Yes.
Principal Kim was looking for you earlier.
Did you see him?
…I have to let her.
Found it.
Got it.
:cue
I mean, how did those brats even get past security?
You have to hand it to the high schoolers in this country.
Father?
Can I get you anything?
Don't bother. Sit.
About that scandal…
No need to explain.
- You're not curious? - There's nothing to be curious about.
I'm sure
it's just a cheap stunt you pulled for attention.
Then why are you here?
It's nearly…
Taeju's mother's death anniversary.
I was wondering if you even remembered.
Ma'am.
She's been standing outside the house for hours,
but she refuses to talk.
Then you should've reported her to the police, not brought her inside.
Send her away.
How can we just send away a child in the middle of the night?
Little one, are you lost?
What's your name?
You don't want to say?
I am
Lee Jooyeon's daughter.
You're my dad…
aren't you?
- Honey! Honey! - Mom!
- Ma'am! Wake up, ma'am! - Honey!
- Honey! - Ma'am!
- Ma'am! Oh, dear goodness! - Mom, wake up!
Since the day your mother abandoned you…
-  Ma'am. - Mommy!
…our lives fell into despair.
CERTIFICATE OF AWARD
Buy me a bike too.
The same one as Taeju.
You dared to be greedy…
REPORT CARD
I want a building too.
One that's taller than Taeju's.
So greedy…
STOCK PRICE ANALYSIS
Amend your will, Father.
In my favor.
Your greed was relentless!
Keep your hands off the company.
And if I don't?
I'll have no choice but to act.
- What? Are you going to disown me? - Why not?
Listen, Mr. Seong Hyeonguk.
You dare call your father by his name?
You just said you'd disown me.
Then you wouldn't be my dad anyway.
So, Mr. Seong Hyeonguk, to summarize,
I shouldn't bother acting out
because it'll all be Taeju's in the end, right?
Seong Taeju will be the ultimate winner.
Taeju is so awesome!
That's the gist. :cue
Right?
I should just kill Taeju and secure my spot in hell.
Seong Huiju!
Anyone who ever tried to pick a fight with me was exactly like you.
They'd stack the deck so they couldn't help but win,
and put me in a spot where I was bound to lose.
I guess they weren't confident
they could win on equal terms.
But you know what?
It's fine.
I'm used to going up against
people like that.
You just won't quit.
I wish you…
all the best.
Though I'm sure you'll lose anyway.
PRINCE
Sorry for hanging up on you earlier--
Are you okay?
Are you all right?
Seong Huiju, can you not hear me?
Can I call you back tomorrow?
What?
I'm a little busy right now.
I'll call you tomorrow.
JUNIOR ALUM
CERTIFICATE OF AWARD
HAPPY BIRTHDAY, TAEJU
HOPE YOU GROW UP STRONG AND HEALTHY
Buy me a bike too.
The same one as Taeju.
REPORT CARD
I want a building too.
One that's taller than Taeju's. :cue
Amend your will, Father.
In my favor.
Who is it?
Someone lost their damn mind.
Who the hell is it at this hour…
Damn it.
♪ Teatime for His Royal Highness! ♪
Your Royal Highness?
Wait, are we playing hide and seek?
What are you doing here?
Wait, are you allowed to be here?
Hold on. Did anyone see you?
Where's Aide Choi?
You play baseball at home?
I have one too many enemies, you see.
Oh.
Wait.
How did you even get here?
Wait, did you come here alone?
Yeah.
You can't just…
Let me get this straight.
You picked these up yourself?
THE SEONG HUIJU COMBO
I will have this one.
Yes, Your Royal Highness.
"Seduce the Prince" Seong Huiju Combo.
It seemed popular.
Seriously?
Couldn't you have left after you finished your work?
- What is it? - Just a bit amazed.
By what?
I came because you sounded so down.
But seeing you eat, you seem perfectly fine.
I was a little down.
I was dragged through the mud all day, you see.
I was barraged with hate comments on social media.
My father suddenly threatened to disown me.
Oh, that's right.
I even got egged by your fans today.
I totally forgot to ask if those eggs were antibiotic-free.
You got "egged"?
Yeah. Two eggs, no less.
Those little pip-squeaks were so damn strong for no reason.
- It still hurts. - Here?
Yeah. Just downstairs.
Are you hurt?
Are you hurt anywhere?
:cue
An investigation is required.
They're coming right now?
That's what I said. Now, move it!
She will be staying here for the time being.
She has been receiving a troublesome amount of attention.
I was concerned.
So you were…
concerned.
And my instructions?
Everything is ready, Your Royal Highness.
Oh!
Maybe that's a bit too close?
Please make yourself at home.
What should I call you?
- Pardon? - How should I address you?
Uh…
I am Yeongmun of the Kim Family, the steward of this residence.
Feel free to call me Steward Kim.
Steward?  Hmm.
Yes, ma'am.
Steward.
It's late, so I will leave you to rest.
I will give you a proper tour of the property tomorrow.
All right.
Just a second.
How shall I address you?
Ah.
I prefer Ms. Seong or Executive Director, but you can call me by my name.
You're not my employee, after all.
Then, I shall
address you as Your Ladyship.
"Your Ladyship"?
Well then.
I was at the palace yesterday,
and today, the prince's private residence.
Yes, Your Royal Highness.
Do you like your room?
I mean, it's nice.
It feels like I'm on a historical drama set.
Why aren't you sleeping?
I have some work to do.
Do you want me to help?
So am I really going to live here now?
Well, it's just that
I'm quite an independent woman.
I find this bustling environment…
a bit bothersome, shall I say?
It's so far from work too.
Shouldn't you be more "bothered"
if I were to leave you in harm's way when I'm supposedly infatuated with you?
Commute aside.
Okay.
:cue
By the way…
You wanted to help.
Is this you helping?
I don't know anything about the royal ancestral rites.
I've never even attended any of my family's.
What do you want to know?
Why are you marrying me?
Isn't it a bit late to be asking that?
We only made the decision yesterday.
Why can't I be a little curious today?
You have a lot of money.
The richest in the country, no less.
Is that your reason?
The most important reason.
It would help the royal family, always under fire
for squandering taxpayers' money.
And what a noble reason it is.
Second.
Beauty.
"Beauty"?
Oh, I guess that finally broke through.
- Third. - What? What now?
Because my family doesn't overstep?
If I say I wish to ascend the throne,
all would condemn me and hurl insults.
But I believe
you would understand me.
The Inner Court Banquet is still some time away.
Yet I am already being pressed to make a decision.
It appears they are quite anxious,
as they need to finalize the guest list soon.
Does Your Majesty have any criteria in mind for the guest list?
I'm not sure.
Those with exemplary character, admirable talents,
and innate nobility?
Would that suffice?
I must cancel today's itinerary.
Pardon?
But they already--
Surely there should be no issue.
I am indisposed, after all.
Your Ladyship, please wake up.
Your Ladyship, wake up.
Wait, hold on.
How dare you storm in here! Hey, you!
Youngseon!
Why that little prick…
What in the world?
What's this about?
Cooperate with the Junghwajeon Hall fire investigation, please.
"Cooperate"?
At the Royal Birthday Banquet,
you entered a restricted area of the palace, didn't you?
I did get lost at one point.
But what about it?
Are you suggesting I started the fire or something?
Nothing has been ruled out yet.
You'll need to give a detailed account of what you did and who you met there.
What exactly am I supposed to explain?
What was that?
You stay here.
You've publicly stated, "The royal family is a money pit.
Someone should abolish the Crown. Let's bring out the guillotine."
Is that correct?
Do you have a warrant?
Under the Royalty and Specialist Protection Law,
suspects of royal threats may be investigated prior to a warrant.
Get started.
Hold on. Take your shoes off.
No, you can't take that!
What do you think you're doing?
- Hold on a second. - You can't take this!
-  What are you doing? - Move!
-  Is this really necessary? -  Please step aside.
What are you doing?
- This is insane. -  Why are you doing this? :cue
Damn it. What now?
Gosh, you're working so hard.
Have you eaten yet?
- You need to eat something. - I'm fine.
Let's fill that belly first.
This is His Royal Highness's favorite, so let's have a taste.
Come on. Take a seat.
Sit down. Let's have a bite while we chat.
Go on. Just try one.
Your Ladyship, you need to eat something too.
Can't be questioned on an empty stomach.
- Go on. It's still warm. - No thanks.
- Come on! - Stop it.
I'm calling His Royal Highness.
Why isn't he picking up?
He probably won't answer.
What?
Cell phones are not allowed during the ritual.
Ritual?
As in ancestral rites?
Ms. Do. You're running, right?
Yes, I'm running.
What a hell of a way to spend the weekend.
What choice do I have? You're the only one I can trust.
Forget all that.
Prepare to give me a hefty bonus.
Hang up now.
I got this.
She won't get in.
Why not?
She's a civilian.
Civilians may enter Jongmyo Shrine only on special days.
Come on.
Oh. Oh!
Huh?
ROYAL PROTECTION BRANCH
Shall we?
-  Hurry up, ma'am. - Hold on…
My goodness.
Wait. I can't believe this.
- Please let me in this once. - No, you can't.
I'm from Castle Beauty.
I need to see His Royal Highness.
We already told you no.
Just leave already!
How can I when I know he's in there?
Ms. Do!
Ms. Do! Oh, Ms. Do!
Ms. Do…
We come by order of the Grand Prince.
GRAND PRINCE I-AN
Good heavens!
That…
Isn't that the Grand Prince's hopae?
Why was that precious thing in the toilet?
- Steward Kim. - Yes?
Please take it to Jongmyo.
- Pardon? - Just in case.
I'm counting on you.
You got this!
Good luck!
Good? Step aside.
I knew it! You could've just let me pass earlier! :cue
Where are you going? It's this way.
That bonus better be a generous one.
I'm so exhausted.
Oh, dear. He can't step out while the ritual is underway.
It's already started.
Oh.
- If he can't leave… - Yes?
…we can go in instead.
What?
Huh?
-  We need to go. - What?
- We need to go. - Pardon?
We need to go.
- How did you even get in here? - Quiet…
We need to go right now.
So…
You're going to question me at the palace?
Seong Huiju!
Mr. Jung.
Your Royal Highness.
I heard the Royal Ancestral Rite was being held at Jongmyo Shrine today.
- What brings you by? - His Majesty is presiding over it.
But what business have you here?
Without authorization from either His Majesty or me.
I gave the authorization.
As I heard the prime suspect in the arson case had been identified.
And since she is…
considered a flight risk and may destroy evidence.
But I did not know that you would be here.
Is there actually any evidence?
As if insulting the Crown with such insolent attire
and threatening others within the palace were not enough,
I hear she was absent
at the time of the incident.
Does that constitute evidence?
Perhaps not.
But it should be enough to tarnish…
her reputation
or her company's reputation.
Wait, my company?
Then have me questioned too.
Every circumstance that casts suspicion on her
applies to me as well.
Will your confidence hold?
I wonder :cue
if yours will hold.
Ms. Seong!
Oh, Your Royal Highness!
- Summon a physician. - I-AN.
Feel free to come to Anhwadang Hall for the questioning.
Summon a physician!
Hurry.
Are you all right, Ms. Seong?
Open your eyes.
Wow.
Wow, we totally slayed!
Slayed, my foot.
How could you agree to come here?
That Mr. Jung or whatever practically dragged me out.
How could I resist?
So…
will I be going to prison?
Does that scare you?
Me?
I'm Seong Huiju of Castle Group.
Prosecutor investigations and search-and-seizure raids…
Stuff like that
is practically an annual event.
I was just wondering which law firm I should hire this time.
- Is that something to be proud of? -  I mean,
it's nothing to brag about, but--
She won't be able to act for now.
She knows pursuing you would implicate me,
which would only escalate matters.
But wouldn't you say that was quite a display?
What was?
Everyone saw it.
The Queen Mother talked about tarnishing my reputation or whatever.
And you taking my side.
Wake up.
Palace staff do not divulge palace affairs.
Do you really believe that?
They say the mouth is the gateway to disaster,
and the tongue is a blade that cuts the body.
Do you know how many mouths were there?
And you think not a single mouth there has loose lips?
They probably whipped up an entire soap opera out of it by now.
I can't believe it.
And still in his ceremonial robe?
I mean, it makes sense.
I heard from an attendant of the Queen Mother…
I thought it was just a passing scandal,
but as soon as she fainted, he swept her up in his arms.
It caused quite a stir.
It must be true love!
I know, right?
Hmm.
Plenty of people weren't there.
That doesn't make someone a suspect.
She must've been so shocked that she fainted.
Your Majesty, are you all right?
Please stay there. I will clean this up.
Court Lady Im.
Is anyone out there?
Court Lady Im!
What are your thoughts?
Pardon?
About what, Your Majesty?
The Grand Prince and that maiden.
Did they seem
genuine in your eyes as well? :cue
- You're not coming with me? - I have to work.
But it's the weekend.
If I clock out,
someone will kill me.
Who?
Him.
Oh.
Try not to stay up too late, though.
I shall try.
You can call me if you have trouble sleeping.
I shall.
The more mouths, the better, right?
Your Ladyship!
Are you all right?
What about His Royal Highness? Is he all right?
Well…
Our dear Steward Kim played a huge role.
I am quite a biker, you see.
Thank you.
Ha!
Applause please.
Well done!
All right!
I'm exhausted.
Still alive?
For now.
I haven't been able to eat, so I'm starving.
Why not? Is the food not to your liking?
No, I'm just trying to lose weight.
Why?
Looking gaunt will make me seem more like a victim.
You'll have the Royal Guard starting tomorrow.
Really?
Is that allowed when we're not married yet?
It isn't.
I see.
"Another crazy stunt pulled by the infatuated Grand Prince"?
I guess you can put it like that.
Should I pull one too?
Never thought I'd be doing this.
This is the least we can do to make them think we're madly in love.
Oh, right.
Here.
This is the tea I drink when I have trouble sleeping.
It's really expensive, so don't waste it. :cue
One more thing…
This is the magnesium supplement I take when I really can't asleep.
The side effect is nightmares, but it's better than not sleeping at all.
- When did I ever ask-- - Stop that.
You didn't see a doctor after what happened, did you?
Don't you think I'd be quite the supportive wife?
Hmm.
What are you doing?
Stay still.
PERFECT CROWN
Why would I blush
and get all fluttery over a measly kiss?
You should have maintained decorum.
Then what? Should we make it a shotgun wedding?
Can I take you somewhere? Let's speed things up a bit.
The quicker we get married, the quicker we get divorced.
Smile!
Do you have that much time - to waste? - I don't.
That maiden should move out of your private residence.
Do you have a plan?
Seong Huiju, what's wrong?
Jeongwoo! The brakes aren't working!
Why aren't you answering?
Will you take their side and not mine
because they're your family?
I will take your side.
I must appear
insanely infatuated with you…
…for people to believe
this absurd marriage is genuine.
- What's that? - It's my hopae.
What about it?
Use it when you need a title behind you
or when you are afraid.
Does it summon a dragon if I swing it around or something?
It'll summon me.
Translated by Justin S. Kim
PERFECT CROWN